http://www.cms.cam.ac.uk/privacy-policy

Privacy policy
HistoryPlanningExtracts from the feasability study - 1997 Edward Cullinan Architects
ConstructionAerial photograph of the building-site
Aerial photos of the site taken by Dr Barry Uscinski on 28 April 1999
CMS in Snow 1998
First public lecture in central-core common room (pavilion A)
Presentation of the Sprague Salver
Scale Model of the Development (front)
Scale Model of the Development
The Artesian Well in the Department of Pure Mathematics and Mathematical Statistics
History
This policy describes what information is gathered when external users visit the Centre for Mathematical Sciences website, and how that information is used.
In common with most websites, this site automatically logs certain information about every request made of it (see below for more details). This information is used for system administration, for bug tracking, and for producing usage statistics. The logged information may be kept indefinitely.
Relevant subsets of this data may be passed to computer security teams as part of investigations of computer misuse involving this site or other computing equipment in the University. Data may be passed to the administrators of other computer systems to enable investigation of problems accessing this site or of system misconfigurations.
Otherwise the logged information is not passed to any third party except if required by law. Summary statistics are extracted from this data and some of these may be made publicly available, but those that are do not include information from which individuals could be identified.
Logged data
The following standard data is automatically logged for each request:
The name or network address of the computer making the request.
The date and time of connection
The HTTP request, which contains the identification of the document requested
The status code of the request (success or failure etc.)
The number of data bytes sent in response
The contents of the HTTP Referrer header supplied by the browser - that is the URL you are selecting the link from
The content of the HTTP User-Agent header supplied by the browser - that is the webbrowser used
Cookies
This website does not currently use cookies except for the Raven authentication process. Raven protected pages are only assessible to members of the University of Cambridge. Any individual sub-sites on this site, who do use cookies will have their own cookie policy.
Access to personal data
All enquiries about personal data in respect of this site should be addressed to the University Data Protection Officer (10 Peas Hill, Cambridge CB2 3PN; tel. 01223 339888; fax 01223 331200; E-mail data.protection@admin.cam.ac.uk).
The University Privacy Policy
The University web site is covered by the The University privacy policy and not by the policy above. Note that some links on the Centre for Mathematics site, in particular the search facility, point to the University site.
© 2020 University of Cambridge
University A-Z
Contact the University
Accessibility
Freedom of information
Terms and conditions
Study at Cambridge
Undergraduate
Spotlight on...
About research at Cambridge
